Okay, so I want to walk you through how
to ingest millions of documents into
your agent memory.
So yeah, basically, we just walk you through over the diagrams, so it will also be easier
to write a piece on this. So
for context, the goal of this
is like how to do the system
design on how to scale the ingestion
logic of the data pipeline
and memory pipeline. How to scale the ingestion
logic to ingest millions of documents into your
agent memory. So this will
be more of an architectural discussion, and it's
mostly related to how can you parallelize these
two pipelines, the data pipeline and memory pipeline, the pipelines
themselves, and also like elements within the
pipeline. For example, all this LM extraction,
embedding, and things like this, right? So you
have like two scaling dimensions.
The pipeline itself and the elements
within the pipeline. And now I'll walk you
through step by step to actually understand. So we have
three elements here, three big elements, the data pipeline,
the memory pipeline, and the unified agent memory.
And in this particular use case, because we are scoped towards the personal assistant
scenario that I'm doing for the book, we will do this
unified agent memory via Nolibre graphs, knowledge
graphs, and semantic search, knowledge graphs and
semantic search and text search
basically. And now, yeah, let's go step by step.
So we have this data work pool, which basically
get as inputs very roughly speaking for this
example, web URLs. But these
web URLs can be like articles, sub stack URLs, YouTube
URLs, or blog URLs, or any other type of sites, right?
Can work basically with any type of URLs and also
RS feeds. This is important because
when you give an URL feed to as input
is just one URL, like one article or one
video or whatever. But when you give an RS feed,
it gives you like the latest 10 videos from
a YouTube channel or latest 10 articles from
sub stack publication and so on and so forth. And
also this feed is like, is changing, right?